

#### **PROFILE**

Born in Cyprus, 20 years old computer enthusiast.

2 Years' experience in Java.

2 Years' experience in C++.

1 Year experience in C#.

4 Horror Game Projects in Unity.

1 Horror Game Project in Unreal Engine.

Basic Web Development and MySQL knowledge.

Worked at a company and designed a professional website at the age of 15.

Active person with passion in Drumming and Music.

Fluent in Greek and English, very skilled at communicating and developing relationships in the workplace.

My goal is to work on huge projects at big companies and create lifechanging video games.

# **CONTACT**

PHONE:

+35799920132

EMAIL:

Kouis16cy@gmail.com

WEBSITE:

www.nikolaskouis.com

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nikolas-kouis-041568229/

## **HOBBIES**

Drumming
Gaming
Game Development

# NIKOLAOS KOUIS

# **EDUCATION**

#### LINOPETRA LYCEUM

2016 - 2019

Field of Physical Sciences and Computer Science

#### **Essex University**

2020 - 2023

Undergraduate of BSc Computer Science, Year 2.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **QS Lysis - Web Designer**

2016-2018

Designer the Official and Professional Website of the company.

# KIK Trading – Mini Mall Stores (MMS)

2021-2021

Summer job as a cashier in MMS in Limassol.

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Pancyprian Discus Throwing Competition Participant
- Grade 6 of Drumming
- Duke of Edinburgh's International Award Bronze Course
- Computer IGCSEs Mathematics IGCSEs First Language Pearson Edexcel - Second Language Cambridge
- Unity Unreal Engine Projects
- Website Designer
- The Loop: Ouroboros, Horror Game, currently on Alpha, using Unreal Engine.
- Ritualist, Horror Game, currently on Alpha, on Unity using C#.
- **Joined the Global Game Jam 2022**, Horror game on Unity using C#, Finished game.
- **Joined the Brackeys Game Jam 2022**, Horror Shooter VR Game on Unity using C#, Finished game.